firstaffair.com 2017-04-07

# Privacy Policy - First Affair

Privacy Policy of the netforge GmbH & Co. KG 

netforge GmbH & Co. KG is very serious about protecting the privacy of its customers. Therefore we would like to inform you when and how your data will be stored. netforge GmbH & Co. KG is governed by the German Data Privacy Protection Act (Bundesdatenschutzgesetzes) and by the State Media Act (Mediendienstestaatsvertrages). netforge GmbH & Co. KG has implemented all technical and managerial measures necessary to satisfy these data protection laws and regulations. 

**Personal Data**

You are able to join our internet service without providing your name or home address. It just requires a valid email address. It is possible to register with an address from a free provider such as hotmail or googlemail. At your nominated email address you will receive information about your profile messages and new offers regarding our service. The email address will not passed to a third party. Additionally IP-addresses will not be recorded or stored during your visit. The IP address will be recorded during payment only to prevent misuse such as credit card fraud. During telephone verification of female customers, the telephone number will be hash coded and stored. The hash code will not passed to a third party nor used for advertisement purposes. The registration and hash coded storing of telephone numbers for full service female customers is required to maintain high standard female profiles and prevent multiple use of one telephone number. 

**Payment details**

For the completion of each payment process, we save all information that is relevant to the payment. This information is saved by us for an indeterminate amount of time. If you order any products, your payment information (e.g. credit card number, bank account information, addresses) and other information will be passed on to and saved by our contractual partner for the payment transaction. For the purposes of credit rating inquiries, the information will be passed on to and also saved by our contractual partners in this area. In case of an outstanding debt, this information will be passed on to our debt collection partner. Our contractual partners for payment transactions are bound by the German Federal Data Protection Act (BDSG). 

**Passing of private data to a third party**

We never pass on personal information or other private data except (as already explained) during the payment process; or if we are required to do so by law enforcement agencies. Your open profile advert can be seen by everybody. Please check the text carefully and do not publish private details such as telephone numbers or email addresses. Be aware that it is possible to find your profile by internet search engines and that your profile may be cached by these services. 

**Right of withdrawal**

If you have passed on personal information you are able to delete this data at any time by deleting your profile after log in. This does not apply to payment process data. To prevent future misuse, we reserve the right to store some personal data such as email addresses or hash-coded telephone numbers if the customer violated our terms and conditions. 

**Use of Browser Cookies**

We do use cookies. They are helpful to gain information such as traffic frequency data. We do not use browser cookies to gain private data of our customers. We also use browser cookies from third parties such as google to analyse information and non private data eg. page visit counts, page impressions etc. You are able to use our service without cookie functionality. 

**Age Policy**

People under the age of 18 are not permitted to join our service. 

**Links to third party internet pages**

Our web pages contain links to other websites. We can not guarantee that these parties are governed by the German Data Privacy Protection Act. 

**Questions and Suggestions**

Please do not hesitate to contact us if you have any questions and suggestions regarding our service and webpage. Thank you very much for taking your time for our privacy statement and enjoy our service. 

Berlin the 13th january 2012
